

ABOUT ME

A musician who codes!! Innovative, creative and a proven team player and a leader, seeking to secure position in software development and collaboratively share my skills, expertise and experience with team and valuable clients.

Started my career with front end development and went on to extend hands in backend along with database management, production servers maintenance/upgradations, team management.

Close to 8 years of experience in building platforms /products in data management/ingestion, data analytics & insights, marketing solutions business sector

SKILLS

Leadership

Engineering Principles

Agile Project Management

Team Building/ Management

Problem Solving

Software System Knowledge

Emotional Intelligence

Docker/Kubernetes

UI/UX Designing

GCP

Java/.Net Core Programming

CONTACT

- +91-8281491678, +91-9140136803
- connect@ayushnair.in

Javascript / UI Frameworks

- www.ayushnair.in
- Bengaluru, India

AYUSH NAIR

Engineering Manager
RESULENT COLLABORATOR PATHEINDER

EDUCATION

College of Engineering, IHRD

Bachelor's of technology in Computer Science

EXPERIENCE

TransUnion, Engineering Manager II

2023 - Present

Leading & building the Analytics & insights team responsible for building platform for generating analytics and insights on Credit and non-credit data for credit marketing/risk use cases. Built the complete machine learning model development lifecycle capabilities along with GenAl data agents for exploration and analytics retrieval on top of structured and unstructured data with data governance. Mentored and expanded the team from member strength of 5 to 40+ within 2 years

Neustar Inc, Software Engineering Manager

Lead the Data Management team responsible for building capabilities for ingesting data from external locations and staging into enterprise data lake. Collaborated with Product, architects to design the data onboarding capabilities of product and deliver to Prod along with team mentoring and handling with constructive feedbacks and innovation

Quero 3, Product lead/ Lead Eng/ Sr Eng

2018 - 2021

Built an ideal CDP platform for marketers, analysts and data scientists which helps to overcome the fragmentation of data, analytics and reporting systems

Dynactionize India, Software Engineer

2016 - 2018

Worked on four different projects developing UI screens using Angular which were focussed on showcasing the potential of Dynizer which was a database in its own.

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Ex-band member of Pank Rockers as a drummer.

Active band member of Ehsaass Music as an acoustic guitarist.